goodyear.eu 2015-06-01

# Goodyear Tires – Made to feel good.

## Privacy policy

On-line Privacy PolicyBasic Confidentiality and Privacy PolicyGoodyear Dunlop Tires Europe B.V, hereafter `Goodyear', considers personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail addresses or telephone number, to be private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by designated staff or authorized agents, and is used only to market our products or better serve our customers. Goodyear will not disclose any personal information to other organizations.

## Information Collection

When you browse a Goodyear web site, you do so anonymously. Personal information is not collected. Some areas of our web sites, however, may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your name, email address, etc., for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, making a purchase, or participating in online surveys.Goodyear may also retain electronic communications you send to our customer service representatives, webmaster or other associates. These may be shared only within Goodyear as a means to continually improve customer service. Goodyear web sites track information about the visits to those sites. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to a site, the daily requests received for particular files on a site, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to customize our web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Certain Goodyear sites may use "cookies" or "web beacons." A "cookie" is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Cookies allow us to better serve visitors to our website by offering a tailored experience. A "web beacon", also referred to as a spotlight tag or pixel tag, is used to recognize unique cookies and assists us in determining which advertisements bring users to a specific website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. If you decline to accept the cookie, it will also disable the web beacon. With both cookies and web beacons, the information collected and used is anonymous and not personally identifiable. The information collected does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address.

## Information use

Goodyear may use the information users give us to, for example, provide a service, measure consumer interest in our various products and services or inform users about new products and programs. These offers may be based on information provided in surveys, information that may indicate purchasing preferences or email sent to a Goodyear site.Any lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information. You may at all times request a copy of your personal information and have it corrected or removed from our database.

## Disclosure

Because Goodyear considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information gathered on-line to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings. Goodyear does not sell, rent or transmit personal information to other organizations.

## Other websites

Goodyear web sites may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
